{"question":"5ч 25мин - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 10мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 45мин - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 50мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 50мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 10мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 40мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 50мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 35мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 45мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 35мин - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 5мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 5мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 40мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 20мин - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 30мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 50мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 25мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 15мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 40мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 10мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 45мин - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 55мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 25мин - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 55мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч - 20мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 40мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 20мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 20мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 55мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 45мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 5мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 40мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 50мин - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 25мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 50мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 50мин - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 45мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 30мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 45мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 10мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 5мин - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 10мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 5мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 40мин - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 15мин - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 30мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 45мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 45мин - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 15мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 20мин - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 55мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 20мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 15мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 5мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 55мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 50мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 20мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 30мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 40мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч - 45мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 20мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 55мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 40мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 25мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 20мин - 50мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 20мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"3ч 35мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 30мин - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 20мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 30мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 15мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 20мин - 25мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 45мин - 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 40мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"2ч 45мин - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 35мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч 55мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 10мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 45мин - 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"10ч 50мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 25мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 35мин - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 45мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 5мин - 40мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч 55мин - 30мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 5мин - 15мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"4ч 15мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"9ч - 10мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 45мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"8ч - 1ч  = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"0", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"7ч 35мин - 55мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"5ч 5мин - 35мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
{"question":"6ч 25мин - 5мин  = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Часы?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Минуты?"}]}
